[
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": " Foster the economic welfare of the EU member states by requiring an application of IFRS for all companies in the EU.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "udymja6okx2e7vf",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Bring transparency by enhancing the international comparability and quality of financial information, enabling investors to make informed economic decisions.",
      "Contribute to economic efficiency by helping investors to identify opportunities and risks across the world, thus improving capital allocation.",
      "Bring accountability by reducing the information gap between the providers of capital and the people to whom they have entrusted their money."
    ],
    "question": "What is not an explicit mission of the IASB?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "... Mandatory contributions of preparers.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "2lijzaay1sy7gi2",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... accounting firms.",
      "... selling books with standards.",
      "... German companies."
    ],
    "question": "The funding of the IASB does not come from ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "... come from different countries.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "ou3w0m1xlhuiupw",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... are always more than 16.",
      "... vote on the application of IFRS in different countries.",
      "... have meetings every week in a year."
    ],
    "question": "The members of the IASB..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "... an EFRAG opinion on the IFRS standard",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "r8cv28fven5q9em",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... final IFRS standard",
      "... an exposure draft",
      "... a discussion paper"
    ],
    "question": "The due process does not involve a ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "... approval process of the EU for newly issued IFRSs.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "s2lhxf7bd8zfedx",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... monitoring of the implementation of existing IFRSs.",
      "... first step of the due process of the IASB.",
      "... enacting of the IAS Regulation."
    ],
    "question": "Endorsement is the ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "... Bilanzrechtsreformgesetz.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "a2oj2k5foxvtd13",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... Deutsche Prüfstelle für Rechnungslegung.",
      "... Bundesanstalt für Finanzdienstleistungsaufsicht.",
      "... Capital Raising Act."
    ],
    "question": "The IAS Regulation was implemented in Germany by the ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Accounting Regulatory Committee",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "703zxuc2qo2szhu",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Accounting Regulation Cooperation",
      "Accounting Rules Concert",
      "Accounting Revision Committee"
    ],
    "question": "What does ARC mean (in the context of international accounting)?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "... is part of total comprehensive income",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "izf2u3vm2plv827",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... arises from transaction with shareholders",
      "... is part of profit or loss for the period",
      "... is recognized in the cash flow statement"
    ],
    "question": "Other comprehensive income ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Enforcement",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "7rmxl1g6m3kb1wr",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Endorsement",
      "Issuing new IFRSs",
      "Issuing new IFRS interpretations"
    ],
    "question": "What is the primary focus of ESMA?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "The IASC issued IASs.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "ymdyolg2iwcqmad",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "The IASC issued endorsement recommendations.",
      "The IASB issues IASs.",
      "The IASC issued IFRSs."
    ],
    "question": "Which statement is correct?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Announcement of the error",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "pyqq5c5xm3mdjup",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Jail sentences",
      "Delisting of shares",
      "No longer allowed to apply IFRS"
    ],
    "question": "What is the most important sanction in the German enforcement system?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Balance Sheet",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "4t1bdwu6aty947h",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Income Statement",
      "Cash Flow Statement",
      "Statement of Changes in Equity"
    ],
    "question": "What is another name of the Statement of Financial Position?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "... whether the standard is enforced.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "8iquf3btrav7tu8",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... whether the standard is contrary to the ‘true and fair view’ (TFV) principle.",
      "... whether the standard is conducive to the European public good.",
      "... whether the standard meets the criteria of understandability, relevance and reliability."
    ],
    "question": "Not a criterion for the endorsement of IFRSs is ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "... all publicly traded companies to apply IFRS in their consolidated financial statements.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "1x6z283u7w9hnjq",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... all publicly traded companies to apply IFRS in their individual financial statements.",
      "... all non-publicly traded companies to apply IFRS in their consolidated financial statements.",
      "... all non-publicly traded companies to apply national GAAP in their financial statements."
    ],
    "question": "The IAS Regulation since 2005 requires..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Time from buying raw materials until selling finished goods.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "t9s3fkh7ir44zlt",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Time from hiring a manager until he/she leaves the firm.",
      "Time from recognizing an item in the balance sheet until its derecognition.",
      "Time from buying inventories until using them in the production process."
    ],
    "question": "What is the operating cycle of a manufacturing company?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Specific standard on the event/transaction",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "d7cbsxzd168u90c",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Accounting literature",
      "Industry practices",
      "Conceptual framework"
    ],
    "question": "What is the most important basis to applied to an event/transaction according to the IFRS hierarchy?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Practical tool to assist users to understand and interpret IFRSs.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "epk31mwg5sy8a0n",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Basic principles for the IASB for the endorsement of the IFRSs.",
      "Practical tool to assist the IASB to supervise the IFRS Foundation.",
      "Practical tool to assist the IASB to coordinate enforcement bodies."
    ],
    "question": "What is the Conceptual Framework of the IASB?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Lenders",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "rygv5vnllgnklct",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Taxation Authorities",
      "Academics",
      "Enforcement agencies"
    ],
    "question": "According to the Conceptual Framework one of the primary users of financial statements are ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Statement of Future Cash Flows",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "mwzeaw7m2xecs2m",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Statement of Performance",
      "Statement of Changes in Equity",
      "Notes"
    ],
    "question": "What is not a mandatory component of financial statements under IFRS?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "... appoints the IASB members.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "ssud18rdbht0vgg",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... issues IFRS standards.",
      "... appoints the IASB monitoring board members.",
      "... is responsible for the endorsement of IFRS standards."
    ],
    "question": "The IFRS Foundation ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Item's cost or value can be measured with reliability.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "u8r7lmqdbymoh5v",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "A resource controlled by the enterprise.",
      "Future economic benefits are expected to flow to the enterprise.",
      "Enterprise received the item as a result of past events."
    ],
    "question": "What is not a requirement for an asset?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Shares of other companies",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "z74fgaf8311umyi",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Bitcoins",
      "Money in the till"
    ],
    "question": "What is not presented under the item “cash and cash equivalents”?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Current and non-current items",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "10cto5sbmqb46tj",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Long-term and non-long-term items",
      "Fixed and non-fixed items",
      "Tangible and non-tangible items"
    ],
    "question": "How is the Statement of Financial Position basically structured?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "... other comprehensive income and profit or loss.",
    "footer": "This is from FA past exam + This is from quiz page",
    "id": "x61u827mhxqmvc9",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... changes in equity from transaction with shareholders and profit or loss.",
      "... other profit or loss and net income.",
      "... profit or loss and other changes in equity."
    ],
    "question": "Total Comprehensive Income consists of ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "gftsg6bdm8im7eq",
    "correctAnswer": " ... carrying amount of an asset exceeds its recoverable amount.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "x190id3wkrnatwf",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... carrying amount of an asset is lower than its recoverable amount.",
      "... book value of an asset is lower than its original cost.",
      "... book value of an asset exceeds its original cost."
    ],
    "question": "An impairment loss is calculated as the amount by which​ the..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "gftsg6bdm8im7eq",
    "correctAnswer": "... the cost of an asset less its residual value.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "l2cp13tpu2ohrug",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... the cost of an asset plus its residual value.",
      "... the process of allocating an expense to an asset.",
      "... the useful life of an asset."
    ],
    "question": "The depreciable amount is..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "gftsg6bdm8im7eq",
    "correctAnswer": "... cost less (minus) accumulated depreciation and any impairment losses",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "4c9snwrsdox5kb3",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... always at initial cost.",
      "... cost less (minus) accumulated depreciation and impairment losses are disclosed in the notes.",
      "... always at fair value less cost to sell."
    ],
    "question": "Using the cost model, PPE is measured subsequent to recognition:"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "gftsg6bdm8im7eq",
    "correctAnswer": "On a regular basis when fair values change, or are expected to change",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "xct8uq4z2gzh0n1",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Always annually",
      "Always every 3-5 years",
      "Never"
    ],
    "question": "In the revaluation model, revaluations are required:"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "gftsg6bdm8im7eq",
    "correctAnswer": "... all components are recognized and depreciated separately.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "rldi6d31mrrxijp",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... all components are recognized and depreciated aggregately.",
      "... all components always have the same useful life.",
      "... all components always have the same cost."
    ],
    "question": "In the component approach, when components have different useful lifes and have significant cost compared to the total cost of the PPE asset...\r\n"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "gftsg6bdm8im7eq",
    "correctAnswer": "35% * (cost of the asset - accumulated depreciation)",
    "footer": "The asterisk (*) in the question is the multiplication operator.",
    "id": "okdaal45c1rpzcb",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "35% * cost of the asset",
      "35% * accumulated depreciation",
      "35% * (cost of the asset + accumulated depreciation)"
    ],
    "question": "For a PPE asset, the depreciation charge for the year, calculated using the diminishing balance basis at the rate of 35%, in case there is no impairment loss, would be arrived at as follows:"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "gftsg6bdm8im7eq",
    "correctAnswer": "Straight-line method",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "4a2g3n3awezgiah",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Diminishing balance method",
      "It does not matter which depreciation method is used.",
      "There is no need for depreciation in t1."
    ],
    "question": "A firm purchases new machines for 11.000€ in t0 and aims at showing a net income as high as possible in t1. The useful life is 5 years and the residual value is 1.000€. Which of the following depreciation models should the firm choose with respect to the new machines?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "gftsg6bdm8im7eq",
    "correctAnswer": "Stock market crash",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "h94hysnsw2h9mop",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Loss of key personnel",
      "Major reorganizations",
      "Physical damage"
    ],
    "question": "Which is not an internal indicator for an impairment:"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "gftsg6bdm8im7eq",
    "correctAnswer": "Each reporting period",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "pskhpkdxbuy4dkv",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Each month",
      "Every 2-3 years",
      "Never"
    ],
    "question": "When do firms shall assess whether there is an indicator that an asset may be impaired?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "gftsg6bdm8im7eq",
    "correctAnswer": "... impaired.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "q8uk8gp1vd8qp38",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... in a revaluation deficit.",
      "... flawed.",
      "... in negative equity."
    ],
    "question": "When the recoverable amount of an asset is less than its carrying value in the Statement of Financial Position, the asset is..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "gftsg6bdm8im7eq",
    "correctAnswer": "The higher of fair value less costs to sell and value in use.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "t0le62ot27s0ptb",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "The lower of its cost and net realizable value.",
      "The lower of net present value and cost.",
      "The higher of net present value and cost."
    ],
    "question": "Under IAS 36, what is the recoverable amount of an asset?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "gftsg6bdm8im7eq",
    "correctAnswer": "When the fair value can be reliably measured.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "7og5mpmnvz556dv",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "When the PPE includes unrecorded intangible assets.",
      "When the fair value of the PPE exceeds the book value by 10%.",
      "When the value of the PPE has been impaired."
    ],
    "question": "Under IAS 16, what is a necessary condition to use the revaluation model to measure property, plant, and equipment (PPE)?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "gftsg6bdm8im7eq",
    "correctAnswer": "Cost model and revaluation model",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "sycp1z635epbnfg",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Cost model and present value model",
      "Fair value model and revaluation model",
      "Fair value model and cost model"
    ],
    "question": "Under IAS 16, which of the following accounting treatments are allowed subsequently to initial recognition?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "c6renzs6o1jr9ps",
    "correctAnswer": "... future economic benefits can be measured reliably.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "g08hyn5kvsipe0l",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... identifiability.",
      "... non-monetary asset.",
      "... no physical substance."
    ],
    "question": "The definition of intangible assets according to IAS 38 does not require ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "c6renzs6o1jr9ps",
    "correctAnswer": "... brands.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "qc1e7ayakhj1ihk",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... money in bank accounts.",
      "... buildings used for rental income.",
      "... machines which are no longer used in the production."
    ],
    "question": "An example for intangible assets are ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "c6renzs6o1jr9ps",
    "correctAnswer": "Acquired brands are always recognized because it is assumed that they generate future economic benefits and that their cost can be measured reliably.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "1bbo93h35fqh40d",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Self-generated brands that will be sold in future are recognised because they will generate future econmic benefits.",
      "Acquired brands are only recognised if they are generated in the development phase and fulfill 6 criteria.",
      "Self-generated brands are only recognised if they are generated in the development phase and fulfill 6 criteria."
    ],
    "question": "What is correct?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "c6renzs6o1jr9ps",
    "correctAnswer": "A firm uses a prototype which was developed by TUM to develop new batteries for electric vehicles.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "ukqkv0h2c2k4711",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "A firm searches for a new process to produce batteries for electric vehicles.",
      "A firm buys a license for a new process to produce batteries for their electric vehicles.",
      "A firm searches for applications of new research findings of TUM to develop a new process to produce batteries for their electric vehicles."
    ],
    "question": "Which of the following are development costs?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "c6renzs6o1jr9ps",
    "correctAnswer": "... all costs are expensed.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "ryepwatin8nf4aa",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... all costs are capitalised.",
      "... all costs are capitalised if 6 requirements are fulfilled.",
      "... all costs are expensed if 6 requirements are fulfilled."
    ],
    "question": "If an entity cannot distinguish research phase and development phase ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "c6renzs6o1jr9ps",
    "correctAnswer": "ability to monitor the development process.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "fxwl0y9vkvnsevr",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "technical feasibility of completing the intangible asset for use/sale.",
      "ability to measure reliably the expenditures.",
      "intention to complete the intangible asset."
    ],
    "question": "Which of the following does not have to be fulfilled in order to recognize development costs?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "c6renzs6o1jr9ps",
    "correctAnswer": "Brands.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "bmbi5a84xeis8cb",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Computer software.",
      "Patented technology.",
      "Motion pictures."
    ],
    "question": "Which of the following intangible assets cannot be recognized if it is self- generated?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "c6renzs6o1jr9ps",
    "correctAnswer": "... the cost model or in the case of an active market the revaluation model.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "oo90zhr65yemjkc",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... the cost model only.",
      "... the fair value model only.",
      "... the revaluation model only."
    ],
    "question": "Intangible assets are measured at the balance sheet date using ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "c6renzs6o1jr9ps",
    "correctAnswer": "... intangible assets with an indefinite useful life.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "22ihh4g0wxpw6r2",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... inventories.",
      "... intangible assets for which an active market exists.",
      "... intangible assets resulting from development costs."
    ],
    "question": "The impairment only approach is used for ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "c6renzs6o1jr9ps",
    "correctAnswer": "Inventories.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "vgd43rsxkw8hh27",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Intangible assets with definite useful life.",
      "Property, plant and equipment.",
      "Intangible assets with indefinite useful life."
    ],
    "question": "For which assets is the impairment test never relevant?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "c6renzs6o1jr9ps",
    "correctAnswer": "Trademarks.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "eyutotltagbsr1u",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Patents.",
      "Computer software.",
      "Machines."
    ],
    "question": "Which of the following assets can have a indefinite useful life?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "c6renzs6o1jr9ps",
    "correctAnswer": "Production quotas.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "94aikouhrtcoyfk",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Patents.",
      "Motion picture.",
      "Trademarks."
    ],
    "question": "For which of the following assets can an active market exist?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "c6renzs6o1jr9ps",
    "correctAnswer": "Capital Asset Pricing Model.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "pizt1pvb303o1v0",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Cost Model.",
      "Revaluation Model.",
      "All listed models are permitted."
    ],
    "question": "Which of the following measurement models is not permitted for the subsequent measurement of intangible assets under IAS 38"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "c6renzs6o1jr9ps",
    "correctAnswer": "Its expected useful life",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "zorzf2sfcixtkoy",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "A period at the discretion of management",
      "Five years",
      "No foreseeable limit"
    ],
    "question": "An intangible asset with a finite useful life should be amortised over:"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "c6renzs6o1jr9ps",
    "correctAnswer": "Profit or Loss",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "l9z39bmxzy22w07",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Equity",
      "Statement of Financial Position",
      "Statement of Cash Flows"
    ],
    "question": "Where is the amortisation of an intangible asset recognised?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "eg8rimxfcn5hxx5",
    "correctAnswer": "Last in, First out (‘LIFO’)",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "75sjg2qq5nr4jkj",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "First in, First out (‘FIFO’)",
      "Weighted Average"
    ],
    "question": "Which of the following cost formulas is not permitted under IAS 2?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "eg8rimxfcn5hxx5",
    "correctAnswer": "Lower of cost and net realisable value",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "v0einwf89gdlz32",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Lower of cost and carrying value",
      "Lower of fair value and net realisable value",
      "Cost of production"
    ],
    "question": "Inventories are measured at:"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "eg8rimxfcn5hxx5",
    "correctAnswer": "Tangible assets lying in the store, which are intended for sale",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "qtwlzxjbwca8e5v",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Machinery used in the production process which is for sale",
      "Productions Plants",
      "Intangible assets used in the production process, but not intended for sale"
    ],
    "question": "Inventories include:"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "eg8rimxfcn5hxx5",
    "correctAnswer": "... Net realisable value",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "0ijwzi76c2jj0xi",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... Fair value",
      "... Market value",
      "... Recoverable amount"
    ],
    "question": "Inventory should be measured at the lower of cost and..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "eg8rimxfcn5hxx5",
    "correctAnswer": "... recognised as an expense in the period in which the write-down occurs",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "t2r4vvsqg3fzafc",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... recognized in the other comprehensive income",
      "... recognized as a current liability in the balance sheet",
      "... recognised as an expense in the subsequent period in which such write-down is warranted"
    ],
    "question": "Any amount of write-down of inventories to net realisable value should be..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "eg8rimxfcn5hxx5",
    "correctAnswer": "The cost of Inventory is $3.700 and the cost of sales is $1.200",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "xq2qprlp1vqjsym",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "The cost of Inventory is $3.7000 and the cost of sales is $1.000",
      "The cost of Inventory is $3.900 and the cost of sales is $1.400",
      "The cost of Inventory is $3.700 and the cost of sales is $4.900"
    ],
    "question": "Zippy Machines is in the business of procuring raw materials and sells them to international markets. During the year, the Company bought four tons of raw materials costing 1.200€, 1.400€, 1.300€ and 1.000€ respectively.\r\nDuring the year it sold only one tone for 1.400€ and follows the FIFO method of valuation. Which of the following statements is TRUE?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "eg8rimxfcn5hxx5",
    "correctAnswer": "Net realisable value",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "nvvfpl2o07ivian",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Recoverable Amount",
      "Market value",
      "Fair value"
    ],
    "question": "The estimated selling price in the ordinary course of business, less any completion costs and costs of sale is called..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "​338.800€",
    "footer": "To-Do: add auto equation generator: 284.400+842.800-(985.500/1,25)",
    "id": "bt1ah1n5n0xx52j",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "230.000€",
      "388.075€",
      "229.984€"
    ],
    "question": "A retail trader fixes his sale price by adding​ 25% to the cost of every item purchased. You are informed that opening inventory was 284.400€, purchases were 842.800€ (equal purchase prices for all items) and sales were ​985.500€. Closing inventory should be:"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "37.500€",
    "footer": "To-Do: add auto equation generator: ((10.000*3+5.000*4+5.000*5)/20.000)*10.000, add table",
    "id": "gy8rg1cm9d6gxln",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "30.000€",
      "56.000€",
      "40.000€"
    ],
    "question": "Handy Ltd values its closing inventory using the weighted average method. What is the amount for the cost of goods sold?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "eg8rimxfcn5hxx5",
    "correctAnswer": "... average cost",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "y5n1743es6mraa1",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... FIFO",
      "... LIFO",
      "... none of these"
    ],
    "question": "In a period of rising prices, the inventory method which is allowed under IFRS and tends to give the highest reported cost of goods sold is:"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "4a9a9l5hitzl4w7",
    "correctAnswer": "A liability with uncertain amount or timing.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "z1nl2gfuy5o22mo",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "A contingent liability with uncertain future cash flows.",
      "A economic benefit to a third party due to a future event.",
      "An entry in other comprehensive income."
    ],
    "question": "What is a provision?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "4a9a9l5hitzl4w7",
    "correctAnswer": "... that it is identifiable.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "njs32l6hza7x2kl",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... that the amount can be measured reliably.",
      "... that the outflow of economic benefits is probable.",
      "... that it results from a past event."
    ],
    "question": "The recognition of a provision does not require ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "4a9a9l5hitzl4w7",
    "correctAnswer": "A management decisions to repair a machine.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "vr2b89mo5lsxeb9",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "A sale contract for products with warranties.",
      "A pattern of past practice of paying bonuses to employees.",
      "A court order to decontaminate land."
    ],
    "question": "Which of the following is not a present obligation from which a provision can result ?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "4a9a9l5hitzl4w7",
    "correctAnswer": "Possible but not probable and not remote.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "xpq5r1wn77hyw62",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Probable but not remote and not possible.",
      "Remote but not possible and not probable.",
      "None of the listed."
    ],
    "question": "What are the probability requirements for the outflow of future economic benefits for a contingent liability?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "4a9a9l5hitzl4w7",
    "correctAnswer": "... best estimate.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "jc3s48brlgtxmw4",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... cost.",
      "... probability weighted fair value.",
      "... net realisable value."
    ],
    "question": "Provisions are measured at ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "4a9a9l5hitzl4w7",
    "correctAnswer": "... the estimated cash ouflow with the highest likelihood.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "ncn2t8dyu7bmu9k",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... the most likely cash inflow.",
      "... the probability-weighted expected value.",
      "... the most likely fair value."
    ],
    "question": "If the risks specific to the liability and the time value\r\nof money are ignored a provision for a lawsuit is measured at ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "15,000€.",
    "footer": "To-Do: add auto equation generator",
    "id": "7u62lqb1gc2gej5",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "5,000€.",
      "10,000€.",
      "20,000€."
    ],
    "question": "An entity sells 2,000 units of a product with warranties under which the entity will repair any manufacturing defects that become apparent within the first six months after purchase. If a minor defect is detected in a product, estimated repair costs of 50€ will result. If a major defect is detected in a product, estimated repair costs of 100€ will result. The entity’s experience together with its future expectations indicate that 90 per cent of the goods sold have no defects, 5 per cent of the goods sold have minor defects and 5 per cent of the goods sold have major defects. What is the value of the provision to be recognized?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "4a9a9l5hitzl4w7",
    "correctAnswer": "DR provision 1 Mio. CR income 1 Mio.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "lqixwe0sigrqw0o",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "DR income 1 Mio. CR provision 1 Mio.",
      "DR provision 1 Mio. CR cash 1 Mio.",
      "DR provision 1 Mio. CR expenses 1 Mio."
    ],
    "question": "An entity wins a lawsuit in 2016 for which a provision of 1 Mio. € was recognized in 2015 for the case of a loss. What are the necessary booking entries?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "zlwndd05kdq4bw4",
    "correctAnswer": "A contract that gives rise to a financial liability or equity instrument of one entity and a financial asset of another entity.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "d6qcnz2w5rb0o62",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "A firm policy that gives rise to a financial asset of one entity and a financial liability or equity instrument of another entity.",
      "A contract that results in a financial asset of one entity and a liability instrument of another entity.",
      "A contract that gives rise to equity instruments of two entities."
    ],
    "question": "What is a financial instrument?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "zlwndd05kdq4bw4",
    "correctAnswer": "Accounts payables.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "y4iw41emjrcg853",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Cash.",
      "A forward with a positive value.",
      "An option to sell shares of an entity."
    ],
    "question": "Which of the following is not a financial asset?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "zlwndd05kdq4bw4",
    "correctAnswer": "Buying an option for selling shares of an entity for 50 Euros and current market value of the shares is 60 Euros.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "bdyxgvaz48yi4dz",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Issuing a 10-year industry bond",
      "Being granted a loan of 1 Mio. Euros by Deutsche Bank.",
      "A forward for buying crude oil in 1 year for 50 Euros per barrel and the current market value of 1 barrel of crude oil is 40 Euros."
    ],
    "question": "Which of the following does not give rise to a financial liability?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "zlwndd05kdq4bw4",
    "correctAnswer": "... amortised cost.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "jhc89pe88846ayg",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... fair value through other comprehensive income.",
      "... fair value through profit and loss.",
      "... net realisable value."
    ],
    "question": "A debt instrument for which the business model is hold the financial instrument and collect the contractual cash flows and for which the SSPI criterion is fulfilled is measured at ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "zlwndd05kdq4bw4",
    "correctAnswer": "... fair value through profit and loss.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "usqdb4car8wgjwh",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... amortised cost.",
      "... fair value through other comprehensive income.",
      "... net realisable value."
    ],
    "question": "Forward contracts are measured at ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "zlwndd05kdq4bw4",
    "correctAnswer": "... only at fair value through profit and loss.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "by4jwdzwdl2ly7i",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... only at amortised cost.",
      "... only at fair value through other comprehensive income.",
      "... fair value through profit and loss or fair value through other comprehensive income."
    ],
    "question": "Shares which are held for trading are measured ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "zlwndd05kdq4bw4",
    "correctAnswer": " ... quoted market prices.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "nljqr7ffzz5bd33",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... discounted future cashflows.",
      "... results of an valuation model.",
      "... best estimates."
    ],
    "question": "The best measure for the fair value of financial instruments (level 1) are..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "zlwndd05kdq4bw4",
    "correctAnswer": "DR expenses 2 Mio., CR financial liability 2 Mio.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "f9ebgp4y8hr9f9z",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "DR expenses 2 Mio., CR financial asset 2 Mio.",
      "DR other comprehensive income, 2 Mio., CR financial liability 2 Mio.",
      "DR other comprehensive income 2 Mio. CR financial asset 2 Mio."
    ],
    "question": "A forward is measured at the balance sheet date. The value was – 2 Mio. at the last balance sheet date and now is – 4 Mio. What are the booking entries?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "zlwndd05kdq4bw4",
    "correctAnswer": "DR financial asset 1 Mio., CR other comprehensive income 1 Mio.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "s6hg693a8ny6jqu",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "DR income 1 Mio., CR financial asset 1 Mio.",
      "DR other comprehensive income, 1 Mio., CR financial asset 1 Mio.",
      "DR other comprehensive income 1 Mio. CR financial liability 1 Mio."
    ],
    "question": "Shares are measured at FVTOCI. The value increased from 3 Mio. to 4 Mio. In comparison to last year. What are the booking entries?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "k26h3ao2dojgp21",
    "correctAnswer": "...has a range of meanings",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "dlbsmasf3uvzmrc",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "...is illegal.",
      "...is considered to always be harmful to shareholders.",
      "...is a valuation technique for intangible assets."
    ],
    "question": "Earnings management..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "k26h3ao2dojgp21",
    "correctAnswer": "Taking a big bath",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "1qpr6uyonvx54pj",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Taking a shower",
      "Jungle Book",
      "Income Balance"
    ],
    "question": "Which of the following is an example of an earnings management pattern?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "k26h3ao2dojgp21",
    "correctAnswer": "The choice by a manager of accounting policies so as to achieve some specific objective.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "f66fnyjlv00ui5y",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Discussions with stockholder",
      "Marketing during slow periods to try and increase sales.",
      "A financial ratio used to better understand the relationship between earnings and sales"
    ],
    "question": "Earnings management is:"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "k26h3ao2dojgp21",
    "correctAnswer": "Real earnings management takes place during the fiscal year.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "dw4ullhgn25ld76",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Choosing a specific write-off period is an example for real earnings management",
      "Accounting earnings management is illegal",
      "Accounting earnings management takes place during the fiscal year."
    ],
    "question": "Which of the following statements is true:"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "k26h3ao2dojgp21",
    "correctAnswer": "Sale-and-lease-back",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "nvp593svb5ts11w",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Estimating residual value",
      "Determining a valuation model for property, plant and equipment.",
      "Not to publish the financial statement"
    ],
    "question": "Which of the following can be an example for real earnings management?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "k26h3ao2dojgp21",
    "correctAnswer": "...flexibility in accounting standards where choices are specified.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "2muatxtxzacgcdp",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "...flexibility in accounting standards where there is no choice.",
      "...flexibility in accounting standards where choices are not specified.",
      "...real earnings management."
    ],
    "question": "The choice between first-in, first-out or weighted average cost (inventories- IAS 2) is an example for..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "k26h3ao2dojgp21",
    "correctAnswer": "All of the listed.",
    "footer": "To-Do: rethink multiple choice",
    "id": "j0xv2eg62dtlplf",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Market data",
      "Financial disclosure",
      "Economic data"
    ],
    "question": "Financial statement analysis makes use of:"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "k26h3ao2dojgp21",
    "correctAnswer": "...gross profit.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "dw5qk8wbczcc34e",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "...net income.",
      "...sales turnover.",
      "...EBITDA."
    ],
    "question": "Deducing cost of goods sold from sales results in..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "k26h3ao2dojgp21",
    "correctAnswer": "...cash flow from operating activities and cash flow from investing activities",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "wqmylukawfyxlt2",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "...net income and cash flow from financing",
      "...EBITDA and sales",
      "...net cash flow and cash flow from operating activities"
    ],
    "question": "The free cash flow combines ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "k26h3ao2dojgp21",
    "correctAnswer": "...the portion of sales that is a profit.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "vb5xd6qmdzfal7x",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "...EBITDA minus depreciation and amortization",
      "...comparison of profit with the investment necessary to generate the profit",
      "...the portion of profit that is sales"
    ],
    "question": "A margin is..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "k26h3ao2dojgp21",
    "correctAnswer": "Net income / Average shareholders′ equity",
    "footer": "The slash (/) in the answers stays for a long fraction. I.e. `A/B` means A is divided by B.",
    "id": "gswvodhtvqfno8l",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Net income / Average Net Cash Flow",
      "Total debt / Total shareholders' equity",
      "Total assets / Total shareholders' equity"
    ],
    "question": "Which returns reflects how much profit a company generates with the money shareholder have invested?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "k26h3ao2dojgp21",
    "correctAnswer": "...gross margin",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "sbl6ktjwmg60yv0",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... net profit margin",
      "...gross efficiency",
      "... EBIT"
    ],
    "question": "Dividing the gross profit by sales results in..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "k26h3ao2dojgp21",
    "correctAnswer": "Sales / Total assets",
    "footer": "The slash (/) in the answers stays for a long fraction. I.e. `A/B` means A is divided by B.",
    "id": "m4umfilaq0akl2m",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "EBIT / Capital Employed",
      "Total debt / Total assets",
      "Current assets / Current liabilities"
    ],
    "question": "Which ratio reflects the average number of times per period that the money invested in assets is converted into sales?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "k26h3ao2dojgp21",
    "correctAnswer": "Current assets / Current liabilities",
    "footer": "The slash (/) in the answers stays for a long fraction. I.e. `A/B` means A is divided by B.",
    "id": "vk1gr76x46pk5ca",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "PPE Investments / PPE Deprication",
      "Total debt / Total assets",
      "Cost of goods sold / Average inventory"
    ],
    "question": "Which Ratio can be used to examine the firm’s liquidity"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "k26h3ao2dojgp21",
    "correctAnswer": "The financial position on a particular date; i.e. assets, liabilities and shareholders' equity",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "gt95v56h4cvcnzw",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Supplementary information on a firm’s business model",
      "The profit or loss for the accounting period",
      "Compensation plans for the board of directors"
    ],
    "question": "What information can be found in a balance sheet?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "k26h3ao2dojgp21",
    "correctAnswer": "The firm is growing",
    "footer": "The slash (/) in the question stays for a long fraction. I.e. `A/B` means A is divided by B.",
    "id": "t3yzp00mragt9tx",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "The firm is shrinking",
      "The firm is bankrupt",
      "The firm conducts earnings management in an illegal way"
    ],
    "question": "A reinvestment rate above 1 indicates? Recall, the Reinvestment Rate (PPE) = PPE Investments / PPE Depriciation"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "k26h3ao2dojgp21",
    "correctAnswer": "Revenues, expenditures, net profit or loss",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "k3iptyj6zv6xwvd",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Daily stock prices",
      "A reconciliation of the beginning and ending balances of all revenue accounts.",
      "CEO entrance date"
    ],
    "question": "What information can be found in an income statement?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "k26h3ao2dojgp21",
    "correctAnswer": "Change in share price, dividends",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "vbepto3udeq5zrc",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "EBIDT, EBITDA, and net income",
      "Total assets, net income, dividends",
      "Change in share price, net income"
    ],
    "question": "The Total Shareholder Return includes:"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "k26h3ao2dojgp21",
    "correctAnswer": "Horizontal balance sheet structure",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "v9a9qafuast481a",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Financial profitability",
      "Total shareholder return",
      "Interest coverage"
    ],
    "question": "The Equity-to-Fixed Assets Ratio can be used to examine the firm’s ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Granting a bank loan amounting to 1.111€ in cash",
    "footer": "Quiz from Mentimeter",
    "id": "q70mgcecb7vd9ts",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Cash sale of goods for 300€",
      "Cash purchase of raw materials",
      "Sales of goods for 600€ on credit",
      "Purchase of goods for 600€ on credit",
      "Taking a cash loan amounting to 95.000€"
    ],
    "question": "What business transaction represents only a Cash Outflow?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Cash sale of goods for 300€",
    "footer": "Quiz from Mentimeter",
    "id": "p1y2ayy56nwjxnx",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Granting a bank loan amounting to 1.111€ in cash",
      "Cash purchase of raw materials",
      "Sales of goods for 600€ on credit",
      "Purchase of goods for 600€ on credit",
      "Taking a cash loan amounting to 95.000€"
    ],
    "question": "What business transaction represents Receipts and Cash Inflow?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Purchase of a production machine for 100.000€",
    "footer": "Quiz from Mentimeter",
    "id": "wov0k2bgheeyg1d",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Sale of tangible assets at bbook value which amounts to 5.000€",
      "Impairment of a company vehicle",
      "A customer pays for a service 6.000€ in cash",
      "Rental payment of a business office",
      "Increase in value for a company's own tangible asset by 100€"
    ],
    "question": "What business transaction represents only an Expenditure?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "A customer pays for a service 6.000€ in cash",
    "footer": "Quiz from Mentimeter",
    "id": "1afsm5b61m183bk",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Sale of tangible assets at bbook value which amounts to 5.000€",
      "Impairment of a company vehicle",
      "Rental payment of a business office",
      "Increase in value for a company's own tangible asset by 100€",
      "Purchase of a production machine for 100.000€"
    ],
    "question": "What business transaction represents Receipts and Income?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Rental payment of a business office",
    "footer": "Quiz from Mentimeter",
    "id": "wl8lmnspalc5wc3",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "A customer pays for a service 6.000€ in cash",
      "Sale of tangible assets at bbook value which amounts to 5.000€",
      "Impairment of a company vehicle",
      "Increase in value for a company's own tangible asset by 100€",
      "Purchase of a production machine for 100.000€"
    ],
    "question": "What business transaction represents an Expenditure and an Expense?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Impairment of a company vehicle",
    "footer": "Quiz from Mentimeter",
    "id": "364qjy9dgnyzp5h",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "A customer pays for a service 6.000€ in cash",
      "Sale of tangible assets at bbook value which amounts to 5.000€",
      "Increase in value for a company's own tangible asset by 100€",
      "Purchase of a production machine for 100.000€",
      "Rental payment of a business office"
    ],
    "question": "What business transaction represents only an Expense?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Receipt",
    "footer": "From Moodle Quiz",
    "id": "e12x38na9otvu2t",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Expense",
      "Income",
      "Expenditure"
    ],
    "question": "The transaction “Sale of tangible assets for its book value of 5,000 EUR.” is a / an ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Cash-inflow, receipt and income",
    "footer": "From Moodle Quiz",
    "id": "y71alzy0vy9hcon",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Receipt and income",
      "Income",
      "Receipt"
    ],
    "question": "The transaction “A customer’s cash payment for services in the amount of 6,000 EUR.” is a / an .."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "D: Write-down of tangible assets; C: Vehicle Fleet 1,000",
    "footer": "This is from FA past exam",
    "id": "eyrwza7i7exf4ye",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "D: D\u0026A; C: Vehicle Fleet 1,000",
      "D: Other operating expenses; C: Vehicle Fleet 1,000",
      "D: Vehicle Fleet; C: Write-down of tangible assets 1,000"
    ],
    "question": "Because of hail damage, a company car suffered a loss of 1,000 EUR that won’t be repaired. Which of the following postings represents the the value decrease correctly?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "... is subject to legal rules.",
    "footer": "This is from FA past exam",
    "id": "dx0aznhf9kbk5sm",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... is customizable for each company.",
      "... is determined by chartered accountants.",
      "... is designed by works council."
    ],
    "question": "External accounting ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "... a cash-outflow and an expenditure.",
    "footer": "This is from FA past exam",
    "id": "fmhzukxwjgff9aa",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... only a cash-outflow",
      "... only a receipt",
      "... a cash-outflow and a receipt"
    ],
    "question": "The transaction \"Purchase of raw materials via cash payment\" is ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "Process Mining software requires event logs, i.e., the user must have access to relevant IT systems.",
    "footer": "This is from FA past exam",
    "id": "yl5tdleigos60q3",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Process Mining is a one-time approach and requires no further attention once the inefficient processes are identified.",
      "Process Mining captures both digital and manual activities in a process.",
      "Process Mining proposes the optimal process for a specific problem."
    ],
    "question": "Which of the following statements on Process Mining is correct?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "The EU endorsement process is necessary because the IASB has no legislative power.",
    "footer": "This is from FA past exam",
    "id": "ogyl1bmpokep55q",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Both German GAAP and IFRS apply the concept of Other Comprehensive Income.",
      "German GAAP is way more fair value oriented than IFRS.",
      "The IASB develops standards for enforcing accounting standards and is responsible for global enforcement coordination."
    ],
    "question": "Which of the following statements is correct?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "Cash flow from business activities.",
    "footer": "This is from FA past exam",
    "id": "2hk1xy5btg3n8zn",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Cash flow from operating activities.",
      "Cash flow from investing activities.",
      "Cash flow from financing activities."
    ],
    "question": "Which of the following sub-cash flows is not part of the sub-cash flows in a statement of cash flows under IFRS?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "performance and cost",
    "footer": "This is from FA past exam",
    "id": "j5n0d1aqb8fvxrn",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "receipt and expenditure",
      "income and expense",
      "cash-inflow and cash-outflow"
    ],
    "question": "The operating result is formed by balancing ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "Receiving a pre-payment on a sale of goods in the subsequent period is a cash-inflow.",
    "footer": "This is from FA past exam",
    "id": "czhvdgba5osduup",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Cash sale of goods is a receipt but not an income.",
      "Cash sale of goods is a expense.",
      "Sale of goods on credit is a cash-inflow."
    ],
    "question": "Which of the following statements is correct?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "only a cash-outflow",
    "footer": "This is from FA past exam",
    "id": "h0yk28gmwbs7t0n",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "only an expenditure",
      "only a receipt",
      "a cash-outflow and an expenditure"
    ],
    "question": "The transaction \"Payment of machinery, that is going to be delivered in the subsequent period“ is ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "D: Expenses for raw materials; C: Raw materials 250",
    "footer": "This is from FA past exam",
    "id": "be5ys2bqupvcr0f",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "D: Expenses for raw materials; C: Finished goods 250",
      "D: Expenses for goods for resale 275 C: Raw materials 250",
      "D: Raw materials; C: Finished goods 250"
    ],
    "question": "When producing a table JUPITER company is consuming wood worth 250 EUR. Which of the following postings represents the business transaction correctly.\r\nAssumption: VAT (Value Added Tax): 10%"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "An integrated report is a concise communication about how an organization's strategy, governance, performance and prospects lead to the creation of value over the short, medium and long term.",
    "footer": "This is from FA past exam",
    "id": "pimlda23eqasitz",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "All of the other mentioned answers are correct.",
      "An integrated report combines CSR and other non-financials in a non-financial report.",
      "An integrated report presents only financial information in detail."
    ],
    "question": "Which statement regarding Integrated Reporting is correct?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "Segment reporting",
    "footer": "This is from FA past exam",
    "id": "jwvz02280iv61u8",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Statement of changes in equity",
      "Statement of comprehensive income",
      "Notes to the financial statement"
    ],
    "question": "Which is not a mandatory component of consolidated financial statements in accordance with IFRS?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "The net realizable value of inventories is assessed in each subsequent period.",
    "footer": "This is from FA past exam",
    "id": "i3oc097uawymyjg",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "The initial measurement of Inventories is done at the lower value of cost and net realizable value (NRV).",
      "FIFO is not in line with the aim of IFRS to provide a market-based view.",
      "In times of increasing costs, LIFO deflates the costs of goods sold."
    ],
    "question": "Which of the following statements is correct?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "only a cash-outflow",
    "footer": "This is from FA past exam",
    "id": "14deox4wpavxid6",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "only a receipt",
      "a cash-outflow and an expenditure",
      "only an expenditure"
    ],
    "question": "The transaction \"Repayment of a loan in the amount of 50,000€\" is ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "Management accounting has to follow certain legal requirements.",
    "footer": "This is from FA past exam",
    "id": "j1cgu6rbf3yi484",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Representing a company's net asset, financial situation and result of operations belongs to financial accounting.",
      "Financial accounting generates information for decision makers outside the company.",
      "Management accounting generates information for decision makers inside the company."
    ],
    "question": "Which of the following statements is wrong?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "Profit affecting balance shortening",
    "footer": "This is from FA past exam",
    "id": "j1ycjtjofp1llvb",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Profit neutral asset swap.",
      "Profit neutral balance shortening.",
      "Profit affecting balance extension."
    ],
    "question": "The transaction \"Depreciation of property\" is a ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "only a receipt",
    "footer": "This is from FA past exam",
    "id": "vkec5xoeu5pi1ah",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "only an expenditure",
      "only an expense",
      "only a profit"
    ],
    "question": "The transaction \"Sale of goods for 700€ on credit\" is ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "Monetary value of a company‘s delivered economic goods within a period.",
    "footer": "This is from FA past exam",
    "id": "cfdmnvr9kroik6m",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Cash and cash equivalents that flow directly to the company within a period.",
      "Monetarily assessed increase in value due to performance of services.",
      "Increase in value within a period (affecting net income)"
    ],
    "question": "Select the correct definition for receipts."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "Provision should be recognised at the amount of 5,000€ and the compensation claim of 50,000€ should be disclosed in the notes.",
    "footer": "This is from FA past exam",
    "id": "mx8c3h8pd7x0oep",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Provision should be recognised at the amount of 50,000€ and the legal costs should be disclosed in the notes.",
      "No provisions should be recognised but both items should be disclosed in the notes.",
      "Provision should be recognised at the amount of 55,000€."
    ],
    "question": "A former employee is claiming compensation of 50,000€ from JUPITER for wrongful dismissal. The company's solicitors have stated that they believe that the claim is unlikely but not remote to succeed. The legal costs relating to the claim are likely to be in the region of 5,000€ and will be incurred regardless of whether or not the claim is successful.\r\n\r\nHow should these items be treated in the IFRS financial statements of JUPITER?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "Inventory count is an area in which warehouse clerks can benefit from the use of Robotic Process Automation.",
    "footer": "This is from FA past exam",
    "id": "qs4rfg7grgkocll",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Natural language processing is a subfield of IoT.",
      "Cloud technology enables accounting departments to obtain required software \"as-a-service\" over the internet.",
      "Visualization can increase data accuracy in the planning and budgeting process."
    ],
    "question": "Which of the following statements on the use of digital technologies in financial accounting is correct?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "D: Rental income; C: Income statement account 12,000",
    "footer": "This is from FA past exam",
    "id": "qa7fui3e6qcb5tn",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "D: Income statement account; C: Rental income 12,000",
      "D: Closing balance sheet account; C: Rental income 12,000",
      "D: Rental income; C: Closing balance sheet account 12,000"
    ],
    "question": "During the current fiscal year all income from rent is generated by a warehouse which is rented out with a monthly rental income of 1,000 EUR. How to close the account 'Rental income' at year end of fiscal year?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "The increase in value is recognized in the OCI after reversing any impairments of previous periods.",
    "footer": "This is from FA past exam",
    "id": "xzqa4nqdwmrxy3z",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "There is not need for depreciation, the Property, plant, and equipment asset is measured at historical cost.",
      "The increase is always completely recognized in OCI.",
      "The increase is always completely recognized in profit or loss."
    ],
    "question": "Under the revaluation model, the fair value of a property, plant, and equipment asset is higher than the carrying amount at the end of the fiscal year. Which of the following statements is correct (assume that the firm revalues its property, plant and equipment each year at the end of the fiscal year)?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "SAP S/4 HANA is SAP’s most recent ERP solution and relies, among others, on in-memory computing and blockchain technology.",
    "footer": "This is from FA past exam",
    "id": "76mnnmhagqq6qiy",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "The event logs of SAP’s ERP systems can be used as an input for Process Mining software.",
      "SAP S/4 HANA consists of several modules, including, among others, Finance (FI), Materials Management (MM), and Supply Chain Management (SCM).",
      "ERP systems support, optimizes and document the information flows within a company’s business processes."
    ],
    "question": "Which of the following statements on ERP processes is not correct?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "Greenwashing is a form of marketing in which green values are deceptively used to persuade the public that an organization's products, aims and policies are environmentally friendly and therefore ‘better’.",
    "footer": "This is from FA past exam",
    "id": "3psorcl4htw9aoy",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Greenwashing is good business practice.",
      "Greenwashing protects consumers.",
      "Greenwashing always goes beyond changing the name or label of a product."
    ],
    "question": "Which statement regarding greenwashing is correct?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "None of the other mentioned answers is correct.",
    "footer": "This is from FA past exam",
    "id": "94mc1dhw8pv3jb4",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Only LIFO and Weighted Average Method.",
      "Only FIFO and Weighted Average Method.",
      "Only FIFO and LIFO."
    ],
    "question": "Which of the following cost formulars for measuring inventories are permitted by German GAAP?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "For certain self-generated intangible assets development costs can be capitalized if future economic benefits are probable.",
    "footer": "This is from FA past exam",
    "id": "k66q7n42mpey41y",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "For certain self-generated intangible assets development costs must be capitalized if future economic benefits are probable.",
      "For certain self-generated intangible assets development costs must be capitalized if an active market exists.",
      "For certain self-generated intangible assets development costs can be capitalized if an active market exists."
    ],
    "question": "Which of the following statements is correct?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "... only an expenditure",
    "footer": "This is from FA past exam",
    "id": "ic6yoavnz2zy838",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... an expenditure and an expense",
      "... only an expense",
      "... a cash-outflow, an expenditure and an expense"
    ],
    "question": "The transaction \"Purchase of wooden planks for 200€ on credit“ is ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Managing director",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "6v7cl9256rgykq3",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Tax advisor",
      "Public accountant",
      "Owner"
    ],
    "question": "Who needs to be appointed for a company being able to be legally represented?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Owners",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "429yp47qnzy6kc4",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Employees",
      "Creditors",
      "Suppliers"
    ],
    "question": "Who is entitled to appoint the management?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Commercial account",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "0233ml3xqjsfg80",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Investment account",
      "Private account",
      "Liability account"
    ],
    "question": "What do you call the account of a company used to process its monetary transactions?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Liabilities",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "x97pqqgmww6pqib",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Assets",
      "Provisions",
      "Credits"
    ],
    "question": "What‘s the technical term for all the debts of a company?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Liabilities side",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "cqoi6d6uxkhjnj2",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Asset side",
      "Capital side",
      "Debt side"
    ],
    "question": "The side of the balance sheet, which includes equity and debt is called ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Asset side",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "pfss23x79k08uim",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Capital side",
      "Liabilities side",
      "Debt side"
    ],
    "question": "The side of the balance sheet, which includes the company's assets is called ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "A customer whom the company has sold goods on credit.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "dtngghk39hlmqht",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "A supplier from whom the company has bought goods on credit.",
      "A Bank which has granted the company a bank loan.",
      "An owner who has granted the company a loan."
    ],
    "question": "Who of the below persons is not a creditor?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "No capital",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "4ek2uv7ok85zpxg",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Liabilities",
      "Debt",
      "Equity"
    ],
    "question": "If a person goes to the commercial trade office and registers a company, this company has ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Creditors",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "oidt6d24c8n4gen",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Sponsors",
      "Debtors",
      "Donors"
    ],
    "question": "What do you call persons besides the owners of a company who provide capital to this company?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Time of payment",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "k131rqdj9stkjxq",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Credit line",
      "Target agreement",
      "Free kick"
    ],
    "question": "If a supplier grants a suppliers credit to a customer for a certain period of time this period of time granted is called:"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Credit line",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "vcpjjdn5lox97tc",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Target agreement",
      "Time of payment",
      "Free kick"
    ],
    "question": "If a bank grants a customer a bank loan over a certain period of time, this is called a ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Investment",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "v9624gbwwwk9yhr",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Depreciation",
      "Valuation",
      "Financial statements"
    ],
    "question": "What is the technical term when a company purchases assets in order to work with it?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Debt",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "0xsxe9oijntkp9f",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Equity",
      "Risk capital",
      "Loss capital"
    ],
    "question": "How to call capital, provided by the creditors of a company?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Capital investment",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "edzggopifxb3b68",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Transfer",
      "Capital withdrawal",
      "Credit"
    ],
    "question": "How to call a transaction in which the owners of a company provide capital to their company?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Equity capital",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "wl5ok66dnsujqqk",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Loss capital",
      "Credit",
      "Asset deposit"
    ],
    "question": "Money invested by owners in their company is called ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Creditor",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "lbiz6ncz5ls0tvc",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Firm",
      "User",
      "Debtor"
    ],
    "question": "Someone providing capital to a company without being its owner is referred to as:"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "Equity capital",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "0n0k2hqcmu6ljxh",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Risk capital",
      "Loss capital",
      "Debt"
    ],
    "question": "What do you call the capital provided by owners to their company?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "dr2w23v6mk00pw9",
    "correctAnswer": "A negative final result increases debt.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "65f3pyljkbo5hj1",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "A positive final result (net income) increases equity.",
      "A negative final result (net loss) decreases equity.",
      "The final result has no influence on debt."
    ],
    "question": "Select the wrong answer:"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "",
    "correctAnswer": "Equity in 02 is the sum of equity of 01 and net income of 01.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "1q55ht8vgdqcd5x",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Equity in 02 is the difference of equity of 01 and net income of 01.",
      "Equity in 02 is the sum of equity of 00 and net income of 01.",
      "Equity in 01 solely consists of net income of 00."
    ],
    "question": "Select the correct answer:"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "Financial situation",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "t23rqz03xguera1",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Percent share",
      "Managing director",
      "Products"
    ],
    "question": "A business transaction changes a company‘s ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "Always applies.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "fcyzwt3ggzffdaa",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Never applies.",
      "Applies to capital investments.",
      "Applies to loans."
    ],
    "question": "The statement \"A business transaction has two impacts from a commercial point of view\""
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "Business transaction",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "44amdj3mosfrkon",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Balance event",
      "Firm event",
      "Company event"
    ],
    "question": "An event causing a change in the financial situation of a company is called a ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "Companies",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "o0n5dc9dp1fj240",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Owners",
      "Creditors",
      "Accountants"
    ],
    "question": "Double-entry bookkeeping considers the business transactions from the perspective of ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "Balance sheet items",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "ej0d919oo3etj0a",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Total assets",
      "Capital stock",
      "Financial situation"
    ],
    "question": "What do you call fixed assets, current assets, equity and debt in general?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "2",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "kduhp0740zbqr2n",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "1",
      "3",
      "4"
    ],
    "question": "How many commercial impacts does a business transaction have at minimum?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "All",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "i6ce21049frpqyw",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "None",
      "Asset-side only",
      "Liabilities-side only"
    ],
    "question": "Which balance sheet items are designed with T-accounts?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "Additions and subtractions",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "1sipy2qsectxx3x",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Additions only",
      "Subtractions only",
      "Neither nor"
    ],
    "question": "What exactly is recorded on a T-account?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "It decreases.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "da1no7c19w6307u",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Nothing.",
      "It increases.",
      "All of it."
    ],
    "question": "What happens to the equity in case of a withdrawal?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "Nothing.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "nlh42s94tl15fd5",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "It decreases.",
      "It increases.",
      "All of it."
    ],
    "question": "What happens to the bank account when purchasing goods on credit?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "It increases.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "nzimmdbapls405g",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "It decreases.",
      "Nothing.",
      "All of it."
    ],
    "question": "What happens to the equity in case of a capital investment?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "Nothing.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "2wzgvd6injdzn06",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "It decreases.",
      "It increases.",
      "All of it."
    ],
    "question": "What happens to the debt account when a machinery is bought and paid in cash?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "... at the outside.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "yb5f35fe0tnsy33",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... on top.",
      "... at the bottom.",
      "... at the inside."
    ],
    "question": "From the balance sheet point of view the debit side regarding fixed assets is ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "... on debit side.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "85a8e256l71tc2a",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... on credit side.",
      "... on the closing balance.",
      "... not at all."
    ],
    "question": "Fixed assets are increasing ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "... decreased.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "4oakolqooioj1tb",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... increased.",
      "... remained equal.",
      "All of it."
    ],
    "question": "The account ‘fixed assets’ was booked on credit side. Thus, fixed assets have ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "It increases.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "gsax3qgk4lfzn7m",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "It decreases.",
      "Nothing.",
      "All of it."
    ],
    "question": "What happens to fixed assets when a machine is bought and paid in cash?"
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "... at the outside.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "8noqhh3928r33tn",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... on top.",
      "... at the bottom.",
      "... at the inside."
    ],
    "question": "From the balance sheet point of view the debit side regarding current assets is ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "... at the inside.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "pe7jhyd869pkh9q",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... on top.",
      "... at the bottom.",
      "... at the outside."
    ],
    "question": "From the balance sheet point of view the debit side regarding equity is ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "... at the inside.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "fzlfblebutammjx",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... on top.",
      "... at the bottom.",
      "... at the outside."
    ],
    "question": "From the balance sheet point of view the debit side regarding debt is ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "... at the inside.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "byau4s867pee7l3",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... on top.",
      "... at the bottom.",
      "... at the outside."
    ],
    "question": "From the balance sheet point of view the credit side regarding fixed assets is ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "... at the inside.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "u5w4qm9tv7rcao1",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... on top.",
      "... at the bottom.",
      "... at the outside."
    ],
    "question": "From the balance sheet point of view the credit side regarding current assets is ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "... at the outside.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "a06oiarrjkdc8r8",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... on top.",
      "... at the bottom.",
      "... at the inside."
    ],
    "question": "From the balance sheet point of view the credit side regarding equity is ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "... at the outside.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "ifc8ow0uszafarg",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... on top.",
      "... at the bottom.",
      "... at the inside."
    ],
    "question": "From the balance sheet point of view the credit side regarding debt is ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "... on debit side.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "hck8umapc483x10",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... on credit side.",
      "... on the closing balance.",
      "... not at all."
    ],
    "question": "Current assets are increasing ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "... on credit side.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "vyjp1gkbdqz182l",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... on debit side.",
      "... on the closing balance.",
      "... not at all."
    ],
    "question": "Equity is increasing..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "... on credit side.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "6ld6n0r3cmz2cn9",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... on debit side.",
      "... on the closing balance.",
      "... not at all."
    ],
    "question": "Debt is increasing..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "... on credit side.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "cv9l3otik5mp9p6",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... on debit side.",
      "... on the closing balance.",
      "... not at all."
    ],
    "question": "Fixed assets are decreasing ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "... on credit side.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "96vgai4br7qtsl6",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... on debit side.",
      "... on the closing balance.",
      "... not at all."
    ],
    "question": "Current assets are decreasing ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "... on debit side.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "vgv1cib3va6nhlj",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... on credit side.",
      "... on the closing balance.",
      "... not at all."
    ],
    "question": "Equity is decreasing ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "... on debit side.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "pwod359d4p684t8",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... on credit side.",
      "... on the closing balance.",
      "... not at all."
    ],
    "question": "Debt is decreasing ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "... decreased.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "x8zcm4nzqueei0h",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... increased.",
      "... remained equal.",
      "All of it."
    ],
    "question": "The account ‘current assets’ was booked on credit side. Thus, current assets have ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "... increased.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "mhcnnfq4p76558z",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... decreased.",
      "... remained equal.",
      "All of it."
    ],
    "question": "The account ‘equity’ was booked on credit side. Thus equity has ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "... increased.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "b5mv8s9fgnhp4fu",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... decreased.",
      "... remained equal.",
      "All of it."
    ],
    "question": "The account ‘debt’ was booked on credit side. Thus debt has ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "... increased.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "193onowhqysre4g",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... decreased.",
      "... remained equal.",
      "All of it."
    ],
    "question": "The account ‘current assets’ was booked on debit side. Thus current assets have ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "... decreased.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "84p2ec5dsbufkxg",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... increased.",
      "... remained equal.",
      "All of it."
    ],
    "question": "The account ‘debt’ was booked on debit side. Thus current assets have ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "... decreased.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "x60735v8qexwvb0",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... increased.",
      "... remained equal.",
      "All of it."
    ],
    "question": "The account ‘equity’ was booked on debit side. Thus current assets have ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "... increased.",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "tjfmu6lru3m231f",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "... decreased.",
      "... remained equal.",
      "All of it."
    ],
    "question": "The account ‘fixed assets’ was booked on debit side. Thus fixed assets have ..."
  },
  {
    "chapter": "hum0cbjc4ow5411",
    "correctAnswer": "Credit balance of 4.000 €",
    "footer": "",
    "id": "m87u8wg197hgucn",
    "otherAnswers": [
      "Debit balance of 4.000 €",
      "Debit balance of 8.000 €",
      "Credit balance of 8.000 €"
    ],
    "question": "On a T-account there are 4 entries on debit side with an amount of 2.000 € each and another 8 entries on credit side with an amount of 1.500 € each. What is the correct type of balance and what value does it have?"
  }
]